<SAMI>
<HEAD>
<TITLE>Hanbange 3.0 - (C) Breadu Soft 2008</TITLE>
<STYLE TYPE="text/css">
<!--
P { margin-left:8pt; margin-right:8pt; margin-bottom:2pt;
    margin-top:2pt; font-size:14pt; text-align:center;
    font-family:굴림, Arial; font-weight:normal; color:white;
    background-color:black; }
.ENUSCC {Name: "English Captions"; lang: en-US-CC; SAMIType:CC; }
#STDPrn { Name:Standard Print; }
#LargePrn { Name:Large Print; font-size:20pt; }
#SmallPrn { Name:Small Print; font-size:10pt; }
-->
</STYLE>
</HEAD>
<BODY>
<SYNC Start=0><P Class=ENUSCC>Subtitle : SAMI Testing<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=5000><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=5950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:00:00:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=10950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=15950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:00:10:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=20950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=25950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:00:20:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=30950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=35950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:00:30:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=40950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=45950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:00:40:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=50950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=55950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:00:50:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=60950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=65950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:01:00:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=70950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=75950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:01:10:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=80950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=85950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:01:20:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=90950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=95950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:01:30:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=100950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=105950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:01:40:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=110950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=115950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:01:50:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=120950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=125950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:02:00:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=130950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=135950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:02:10:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=140950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=145950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:02:20:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=150950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=155950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:02:30:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=160950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=165950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:02:40:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=170950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=175950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:02:50:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=180950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=185950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:03:00:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=190950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=195950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:03:10:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=200950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=205950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:03:20:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=210950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=215950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:03:30:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=220950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=225950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:03:40:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=230950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=235950><P Class=ENUSCC>[SAMI] 10:03:50:00:00<br>&nbsp;<br>&nbsp;
<SYNC Start=240950><P Class=ENUSCC>&nbsp;
</BODY>
</SAMI>